http://www.webtechholmfirth.co.uk/privacy/

HomeServicesWebsite developmentEcommerce websitesHosting and domainsSearch engine optimisationBlog, newsContact Me 01484 688414
HomeServicesWebsite developmentEcommerce websitesHosting and domainsSearch engine optimisationBlog, newsContact Me
Privacy Policy and Accessibility Statement.
Introduction.
WebTech Holmfirth (also referred to as “WTH” and “the company”) takes the confidentiality of personal data very seriously. Please email us if you have any questions or comments on this privacy policy.
WTH’s privacy policy sets out the ways the company processes personal data. This privacy policy only relates to personal data collected by the contact us form via the WebTech Holmfirth website. Any personal data collected by the company is used in accordance with data protection legislation.
This privacy policy does not apply to personal data provided to WTH by any other means or via any other website. Users should be aware that if they provide personal data to other companies, the privacy policies of those companies determine the use to which the information is put and WTH’s privacy policy will no longer apply.
The Data Protection Act 1998.
The WebTech Holmfirth website complies with the principles of the Data Protection Act 1998
Use made of personal information.
Personal information provided in a contact us form via the WebTech Holmfirth website will be used for the purposes outlined at the time of collection.
In addition, personal information may be used for statistical analysis.
Personal data will be collected and processed by WebTech Holmfirth for the following purposes:
To provide information via email on services provided by the company; administration and marketing, advertising and promotions, unless a user elects to opt out of receiving such communications; notification of events, workshops and training sessions, unless a user elects to opt out of receiving such communications.
Processing personal data for the above purposes may entail sharing the information with employees, contractors, agents and professional advisers of WTH. However, written agreements exist between the company and such parties that there must be no disclosure or further processing of such personal data.
Accessibility statement.
Webtech Holmfirth  is committed to providing a website that is accessible to the widest possible audience, regardless of technology or ability. WTH are actively working to increase the accessibility and usability of our website and in doing so adhere to many of the available standards and guidelines.
Web Accessibility Initiative.
This website endeavours to conform to priority level 1 of the World Wide Web Consortium (W3C) Web Content Accessibility Guidelines 1.0.
These guidelines explain how to make web content more accessible for people with disabilities. Conformance with these guidelines will help make the web more user friendly for all people.
W3C Standards.
This site has been built using code compliant with W3C standards for XHTML and CSS. The site displays correctly in current browsers and using standards compliant XHTML/CSS code means it will also display correctly on any future browsers.
Exceptions.
Whilst WebTech Holmfirth strives to adhere to the accepted guidelines and standards for accessibility and usability, it is not always possible to do so in all areas of the website.
We are continually seeking solutions that will bring all areas of the site up to the same level of overall accessibility. In the meantime should you experience any difficulty in accessing the WebTech Holmfirth website, please don’t hesitate to contact us.
Send me a message
To send a message fill out the form:
No sales calls please.
Customers and friends: I vet calls and will pick up if I'm availble or return any messages left.
Copyright © 2020 Webtech Holmfirth System status | Site map | Privacy | Cookies | Website design by Webtech
